Guide to the Secretary's Office, Yale University, Records Concerning "The Yale"
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Secretary's office, Yale University, records concerning The Yale
1999-2004
RU 951
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1
1 box
1228.8
The records consist of correspondence, advertising records, computer files, an editor's log, working copies, and budget information documenting the publishing of The Yale: A Guide to Yale and New Haven.
Yale University. Office of the Secretary
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 4-A (YRG 4-A), Records of the Yale secretary's office.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the Office of the Secretary, 2004.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged chronologically.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, advertising records, computer files, an editor's log, working copies, and budget information documenting the publishing of The Yale: A Guide to Yale and New Haven.
College publications; Yale University. Office of the Secretary
- Records of The Yale, 1999-2004; Accession 2004-A-139
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2039
  - Final report, 1999-2000 (Box 1)
  - Advertising (Box 1)
  - Distribution (Box 1)
  - Ad Contracts (Box 1)
  - Financial Report, 2000-2001 (Box 1)
  - Internal distribution (Box 1)
  - Ad contracts (Box 1)
  - Working copy (Box 1)
  - Working copy, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
  - Financial statement (Box 1)
  - Ad packet (Box 1)
  - Ad contracts (Box 1)
  - Web site (Box 1)
  - Budget, 2002-2003 (Box 1)
  - Progress report (Box 1)
  - Ad packet (Box 1)
  - Ad contracts (Box 1)
  - Web site (Box 1)
  - Budget, 2002-2003 (Box 1)
  - Progress report (Box 1)
  - Ad packet (Box 1)
  - Ad contracts (Box 1)
  - RIS Production schedule (Box 1)
  - Departmental letters (Box 1)
  - LKL letters to Deans (Box 1)
  - Editors log (Box 1)
  - Cornell Student Handbook, 2003-2004 (Box 1)
  - Master 2002-2003 (Box 1)
  - Budget (Box 1)
  - Notes Management Meetings (Box 1)
  - Email to editors (Box 1)
  - Management meetings (Box 1)
  - Advertising correspondence (Box 1)
  - Ad Packet (Box 1)
  - Advertising contracts (Box 1)
  - Dean's orders (Box 1)
  - Internal orders (Box 1)
  - Final Advertising report (Box 1)
  - Final Internal Orders Report (Box 1)
  - Style Sheets (Box 1)
  - Computer files, 1047; (45 JPG, 101 TIF, 32 HTML, 1 PDF, 1 MPEG, 6 DOC, 3 TXT, 2 WPD, 31 Encapsulated PostScript, 4 Quark Xpress Data File, 1 OLE Compound Document, 1 AutoCAD Script, 1 MAC OSX Stationary, 1 Interleaf Document). (Box 2)
    Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
    - INDORF
    - Gourmet Heaven photos, credit Thomas R. Violante
    - Chapter 12 images, ads & fonts from "The Yale," David D'Addio's files, 2000-2001
    - Barnes & Noble Ad 2003-2004 Satellite Graphics
    - GIST - TY covers 99-00, 1999-2000
    - Blue page Ad, 2002-2003
    - The Yale Directory Listing, 2002-2003
    - Yale Guide Ad, Y4 PG Fonts=Outlines, 2001-2002
    - The Whole Enchilada ad art, "Typo Cuisine"
    - Photo for Stacy B ad
    - Whole enchilada, images, logos, ad
    - Omni NH Hotel ad, B&W full, EMS Clamations!
    - Tyco Ad The Yale
    - Stacy B, Jolynne, 3 pics
    - Trailblazer ad
    - Photo CD 0018 3191 0400, 5 May 2001
    - A.V. scans for The Yale, 1999-2000
    - Photo CD 012633112123, 30 May 2001
    - Photo CD 012633112124, 30 May 2001
    - Photo CD 932132621895, The Yale scans, 23 May 2001
    - Photo CD, 23 May 2000
    - Photo CD, 22 May 2002
    - Photos for The Yale
    - Matches Book, Chapter 9 - End fonts (Disk 2 of 2), 2002-2003
    - 2000-2001 Copy from Can. The Yale Final
    - The Yale Cover's, Inside and Outside, 2002-2003
    - Yale cover, 2000-2001
    - The Yale 2001-2002, Covers
    - The Yale 1996-1997, 1997-1998, 1998-1999, 1999-2000, 1996-2000
    - Copy of The Yale 1996-1997, 1997-1998, 1998-1999, 1999-2000, 1996-2000
    - Copy matches Book, chapters. 1-8 of The Yale 2002-2003
    - The Yale 2003-2004, files & fonts, no cover.
    - The Yale 2003-2004 Orders Advertising, Student organizations
    - The Yale 2001-2002, all files, photos, fonts, and covers